[Music]
holy [__] [__] this place is freezing
my balls off you think you have it bad
look at my hair [__] does your frozen
hair make you look like a goddamn
unicorn made of popsicles shut your
frost bitten mouth before I pound your
ass
sent to guard duty on a high security
prison on a frozen wasteland [__]
what's even there to guard it from
nothing but snow and ice and Shut the
[__] up little bro i think there's some
poor bastard just face down in the snow
out there the [__] are you saying i
thought Princess Celestia said this
planet was civilian proof don't know
little dude but we should check it out
or Sunbutt's going to burn our ass
hey it is a horse looks like another
dead inmate tried to escape and froze to
death [__] hey go get me a Pepsi Mini
from the fridge i'm going to call this
one in real
quick oh [__]
[Music]
and that's what was said to me on my
Android phone as the guard lay dying
copious amounts of blood and rancid [__]
pouring from the wound that was once his
gaping [__] pierced by a blade of
sharpened steel the five of you have
been specifically chosen for this top
priority mission three unicorns because
you are good and a pegasus and earth
pony of normality your objective travel
to the harsh and forboding planet of
Napon and halt this curious assassin
from reaching the highsecurity prison of
Frost Hold Penitentiary why would some
creepy mayor go to a prison don't most
of them want to get out that's a good
question Derpy my mom says asking lots
of questions masks my autism in public
it doesn't you see Frost Hold
Penitentiary only houses one inmate a
young mare named Wallflower Blush a
whole planet just for one little pony
what for what makes her so dangerous
wallflower Blush is no ordinary prisoner
her very nature is that of a magic seal
which nullifies spells in a massive
radius if any pony gets their hooves on
her they could easily use Wallflower's
abilities to their own advantage
so she's essentially a walking no fun
allowed sign for unicorns that sounds
pretty racist look the point is you
can't let this stranger reach Wallflower
but be warned even Wallflower may
attempt to pull you to her side with her
unyielding cuteness use the spaceship
parked in my backyard to reach Neptune
secure Wallflower before the assassin
and rendevous with Princess Luna who
will be waiting at the extraction point
with her fourperson bicycle won't there
be seven of us that is very astute of
you Miss Palmare yes I would not be
sending this many of you if I didn't
expect casualties and one last thing
you'll be joined by a specialist who
knows the prison's layout both inside
and
out i'm Queen Chrysalis from My Little
Pony Friendship is Magic i'd like to
apologize to anyone who I've made feel
uncomfortable but I'd mainly like to
apologize for being a and a pissist but
if simply apologizing isn't enough for
you no I am also going through cognitive
behavioral therapy currently I stand at
a 0% success rate so today let's see if
I can bump those numbers up
so Chrysalis how are you holding up as a
reformed villain so far pretty good all
things considered except for my
crippling sexual obsession for
Twilight's family hey what a coincidence
twilight Sparkle happens to be my [__]
what is it about that family that drives
girls like us mad shining armor is just
so Do you know what it's like to have
loved the same man for 27 years isn't he
only
36 hurry up back there with my luggage
and you better not break anything okay
so Charlie have you ever piloted one of
Celestia's highly advanced spacecraft
before no but it's just physics and
aerodynamics orbital mechanics are
child's play compared to the complex
beauty of mathematical theory so no but
I'm always up for trying new things yeah
it seems you've been trying loads of new
[__] these days what is that supposed to
mean oh nothing don't you nothing me bro
spill the beans look I was going to save
this talk for after this
life-threatening mission but seeing as
we might not survive this Twilight you
uh you accidentally sent a video to the
family chat and it had you doing some
pretty gross [__]
sweet Luna that show was exhausting my
pits are practically feral right now
what the What do you got that old video
camera out for you filming some kind of
home video or
something thought so you perve get that
flank over here you dirty girl you're so
much better down there get licking
[__] that's it baby girl god it's
pathetic sparkle you're so far gone to
think you were once the great and
powerful Trixiey's most powerful rival
now you're just her sweaty pit licking
mess what's so weird about that look I
already talked with mom and dad and are
fine with you liking girls lesbians are
smoking hot but like the least you could
do is be the man in the relationship
really you want to discuss my sexuality
now why not you are perfectly fine
making it every pony's business in the
[__] family group chat twilight it's
over you need to own this you have to
establish yourself as the stallion in
this relationship because right now
you're looking like a [__] so like did
mom and dad see the video just me sis i
wanted to give you a chance but I will
show it to them if you don't put a stop
oh darling it seems we've been hit by a
barreling asteroid every pony buckle
your seat belts to avoid being sucked
out to the vacuum of space i can't get
the seat belt over my bodacious bubble
biscuits these seats aren't made for the
finely sculptured ass of a
woman
[Music]
help no no no no it didn't have to be
like this oh God chrysalis why why did
this have to happen you may have been an
evil rap but you were my evil pet
not even you deserved such a terrible
fate
hey uh white boy i'm not dead you know
chrissy what the [__] chrissy uh um
you're alive it's a miracle a divine
miracle nah I'm not a miracle i'm just a
bug we changelings can survive quite a
long while without bodies pretty cool
huh ow
much better thanks a ton lover boy shut
the [__] up we need to hurry and find
shelter before we die out here shiny are
you worried about me as if I'd cry over
a race lesser than a [__] horse don't
be gross you sure Twinkle Toes cuz I
distinctly remember you sobbing like a
[__] in heat over my tight little
exoskeleton crying how the world would
never be the same without that nasty bug
[__] and wishing you could have one
more taste of that premium dark
chocolate tell any pony about this and I
will personally have Princess Celestia
launch your ass into the sun this cold's
really nipping at my nipples hey baby
see if you can start a fire will you
trixie does not feel so good oh baby
you're burning up this must be that
[__] magic nullification Celestia was
talking about get back inside the ship
and mom will make you a nice hot bowl of
Campbell's chicky noodle soup
um hello what about our job what if we
get attacked by that assassin lady
wow i cannot believe what I'm hearing
derpy I thought you cared about Trixie i
barely know her and she's bald why would
I care about that loser i am not then
let me put it this way have a little bit
of hair need I remind you Luna is
waiting with her fourperson bicycle i'm
the leader so naturally one seat is
locked the [__] in for me leaving only a
hoof full left if I were one of you
unfortunate souls by Luna's fluffy tale
I'd think awfully hard about whose good
graces I'd want to be in by the end
gotcha well here we are high security
wing cell number
four there she is that little freak hey
your wallflower blush right we're here
to rescue you
hey we're talking to you
wa you're green that's like a super rare
color for ponies
oh oh awkward i wasn't expecting any
visitors this year or ever really is
today my execution day oh for my last
meal can I have uh Long John Silvers
okay important question are you a boy or
a girl if you're a boy can I fondle your
balls for free you two girls seem
surprisingly kind for prison guards you
seem surprisingly kind for a pony
banished to the edge of the galaxy hey
are those Legos i love Legos can I come
in and play with you you seem really
lonely there used to be others in this
building that would scream so to make
the noise stop I ate them great that'll
make our escape so much easier can you
walk sure I can walk just not with this
thing on if you unbuckle me that would
really help okay the [__] you mean okay
for didn't you hear what you just said
but look at her she's adorable so tell
me a little about yourself for starters
ponies happen to find me exceptionally
fish for my odd ability to warp the mind
of anyone I see fit honestly same but
like in a sex way
hey you lied to us i'm sorry but I don't
have a choice you seem really nice
though so run away with me and help me
escape or else I'll lock you in that
cell with your friend and let you freeze
you want me to take care of my child
from behind bars
holy [__] derpy [__]
you know you could just admit you're
cold i might even share some of my
winter coat if you do i am not cold sure
you aren't
i read something on the internet the
what now the vast network of information
changelings tap into when we need to
learn things quickly computers were
after my time anyway it said one way to
get warm in extreme conditions is to
snuggle up with I'm going to cut you off
right there cuz I don't give a [__] fine
then enjoy watching me slowly freeze to
death you're not going to freeze to
death oh how tragic the mighty changing
queen perishing in an icy cold cave when
all she needed was a little bit of
warmth if only some pony had shown an
ounce of compassion okay fine whatever
but Cadence can't hear about this wait
really
my You really are warm i can see why
Cadence keeps you around don't get too
comfy this is still a survival situation
not some freakish bonding moment
whatever you say Cuttlebug
[Music]
so what are we going to do now that
you're free going to go rob a bank maybe
take over Equestria with your anti-agic
powers no nothing like that Derpy i've
done so many bad things things I don't
even think I deserve to be forgiven for
but I'm not that girl anymore and I
haven't been for a long time i don't
want to spend the rest of my life locked
in a cell then don't judging ponies for
something they did in the past is stupid
even ponies who did really really bad
things every pony messes up sometimes
wallflower some worse than others sure
but if we all just decided one day that
bad ponies can't become good ponies then
there wouldn't be any reason to try and
improve nothing but hollow
[Music]
echoes i should have known it was you
Derpy who is that lady
i'm a collector of hearts you see but
not just any kind special ones that hold
great value like yours Miss Blush a
heart which coils with hatred what are
you talking about i'm not evil just
mildly autistic aren't you haven't you
hurt others haven't you erased memories
and made the world forget your sins
ponies like Derpy and Twilight Sparkle
all these so-called heroes they believe
that redemption is for every pony but I
know the truth that some hearts are
beyond
salvageable a pure heart this is
unexpected but a pure heart is good too
you monster give it back
you're really starting to get on my
[__]
nerves
wait you're the one who stole my
employees heart right return Koko's
heart and I'll give you mine in her
place you want an evil heart right i lie
I cheat if there's any pony who has the
heart you're looking for it's me i
require hearts of extreme feelings ones
rotted beyond saving or hearts of
unshakable purity your heart is just too
normal you're selfish that's true but
you regret and that makes you an
unremarkable girl then Twilight and
Trixie will stop you trixie
yeah [__] they're both here and they're
going to kick your ass
oh it's [__] over is this seriously
how I'm going to die splatting the
ground like a pancake on this alien
world is this your doing bulk is this
your final act of revenge against me to
drag me down to hell with you the way I
did to you if it is then [__] it let's
go all the way to hell when I get down
there I'm kicking your ass
[Music]
don't even think about it Derpy you know
this isn't what Bulk would have wanted
but I killed him i made him my [__]
[__] and now he's dead let's be real
here girl aside from your gross eyes
you're honestly kind of a fine piece of
ass i don't think any pony would mind
being your [__]
why are you naked
hey so uh how's the wallflower hunt
coming along
ah what do you think you're doing
washing you so this was your plan all
along lure the great and powerful Trixie
away so you could try something
scandalous if you're trying to set the
mood you could at least light some
candles first it's only a shower baby
that's it the great and moisturized
Trixie is getting out of this tub she
refuses to be subjected to any more of
Sparkle suspicious handling any
longer aha I knew it the culmination of
your insatiable lust for the wet and
moisturized Trixie on full
[Music]
display how are you feeling honey better
now with the stuffy brigade defending me
from all angles thank you sugar
plum so any news from the
girls derpy has failed us all
twilight where in the ever loving [__]
are you still on the other side of the
solar system but listen there's this
pony wearing a mask i know i'm looking
at her right [__] now she's here at
the theater in Lost Pegasus and there's
this magician on stage it looks like
she's going to jump him well stop her
you [__] [__] twilight sorry Mommy
light a fire under those plump juicy
cheeks and return home pronto i'm unable
to make any moves
princess you are a goddess what could be
stopping you from acting at a time like
this
taking a fat dump
move i'm gay i just do her because I'm
sexist towards women it's more like a
dominance thing for me than Trixie come
on yes mommy
all right Billies and gentle cults for
my grand finale I shall attempt a trick
so daring so impossible that you'll be
talking about it for years to come
actually I think I'd like to perform a
trick of my own if that's okay oh dear
every pony looks like a stray cat got
lost and found her way on stage
meow
you messing with me kid
you're the one who called me a cat i
just figured I'd play the part
i don't deal with psycho fans little
girl if you want that mask signed you're
going to have to buy a ticket like every
pony else now scram
how unfair is it that you stallions get
to stand in spotlights admired by so
many while users battle for
scraps you play the character of a
charming magician so well even I
believed you for many years
jackpot but what would your adoring fans
think if they knew the real you all
right this is getting cute but the
show's over now every pony go home where
you used to live do you ever think about
that tiny apartment the one above the
laundromat
i don't know what you're talking about
you left that apartment behind for a
house in Las Pegasus with a balcony you
traded her for a balcony
you whispered all the right words to her
told her you were different and made her
feel special you said you'd always be
there for her but the minute she became
pregnant with your bastard children you
covered it up with fame and money like
all the rest
cut the crap who the hell do you think
you are huh i'm the star of this show
here
i am the face your sins created the
shadow of the life you threw away the
bringer of justice for my mother
and the one who will kill you
[Music]
trixie
she she looks just like you
oh and one more thing i'm also
[Music]
sexist another run to save somebody's
life and have her glow up in his face
i'm not the only one who finds it hard
to understand i'm not afraid of God i am
afraid of man running in our blood is it
running in our veins is it running in
our genes is it in our DNA humans are
going to behave as we think we are
should yeah we can be bad yes we can be
[Music]
good we're
just anything at all heat heat
[Applause]
now Dad for the final trick of the night
it's time to make the magician disappear
stop trixie Lulaoon your face is nothing
like the
posters we really do look a lot alike
huh what are you going to do to him
shouldn't that be obvious revenge
against that man for what he did to mom
you're going to steal his heart that
would be pretty funny wouldn't it after
all it's what this homo deserves but no
I don't want his disgusting heart this
prey needs to be personal that's why we
figured you should be a part of this too
we
Come on the fucker's a hardcore drunk so
I spiked one of his cocktails before the
show i doubt he'll get very far
[__] dad you don't look so good and
after one little glass who knew you were
such a [__]
lightweight flawless
hey Mom
don't call me that
your daughter is the one who helped me
find you Trixie
imagine the shock when I found out I had
a long lost sister who uh got busy
is that what she told you oh Trixie do
you really think lost souls just find
each other in this world no no often
even fate needs a little guidance
that girl was forgotten like a stray
piece of a puzzle waiting to be placed
where she belonged so I brought her to
that place you manipulated her she
liberated me she told me the truth
trixie how your magic is so strong you
were able to impregnate a mayor with
more powers like yours we won't have a
need for stallions anymore what are you
saying i was born [__] up because you
ate up all of the magic before I was
even born you were granted extraordinary
powers while I spent my life barely
clinging on sad isn't it to think all
this time you were living your happy
little life while she suffered in
silence i didn't know of course you
didn't you never even knew I existed but
you can make up for it now by killing
the stallion responsible for my
suffering the one who used our mother
and set all of this in motion
[Music]
trixie please i loved your mother you
know I did
that's enough
you girls made your point we don't need
this to become some twisted spectacle
for all of Equestria to see stop you
want me to stop he deserves this
Twilight because of him my mom is no he
doesn't deserve this and you know it
regardless of how much he hurt you this
isn't the right way to settle this you
used to be a terrible girl who didn't
care about others but I gave you the
chance to prove me wrong and you did so
can't you do the same for him what's
with this melodramatic [__] every
little pony has the right to revenge
that's just how the world is he hurt you
so hurt him back besides would the world
really miss him
it's men like him that makes the world a
more dangerous place for girls like us
[Music]
honey put the knife down it'll be okay
twilight eye i'm
sorry i'm not like you
[Music]
feelings i'm trying hard to forget
you trying hard
to voice every
[Music]
What are you doing holding you
does your chest hurt
a little
it's going to hurt a whole lot more when
our friends find out what you did
twi
thank you Trixie
but you seem now that dad's dead i'll
need a new heart if I'm going to bring
mom back want to know something weird
since the day I was born I could see
pony's hearts they all burn like flames
but they have different colors and
intensity they look different depending
on the pony and yours is a truly evil
heart you can't be serious she's your
sister you stole the first half of my
life so I'm taking your second my magic
for your heart sounds like a pretty fair
trade to me that wasn't my fault i know
though that doesn't make me hate you any
less but even if I do hate you I'm still
glad we got to share one moment together
as sisters
[Music]
he he mama that tickles i know my little
star what are you doing mama i'm casting
a magic spell one I made just for you
why because I'll be going away soon and
that means I won't be there to do the
things I normally do
when will you be back can I come no no
Trixie you'll have to stay here but I
want to go with you i don't like it here
i only get two half carats a day and
they won't even let me watch TV how
about a gift instead if some mean old
bullies ever try and hurt you while I'm
away just once and only once you can
reverse the act on them instead it'll be
like I never left
[Music]
i don't get it why would a pony hurt
another pony we're all just ponies
and maybe it wouldn't even
matter if it
[Music]
always
disaster so I'm just a
swag i'm just a swag you spent your
whole life blaming me and maybe you were
right too maybe everything that happened
to you really was my fault but even if I
could change it if I could somehow undo
everything
I can't say that I would i've done too
much in my life to trade it away made
friends
enemies i even met the girl of my
dreams i can't lose that you would have
liked her she's annoying as hell
sometimes but she always tries to do the
right thing even when she doesn't know
what the right thing is she would have
definitely tried to help you you know no
matter what kind of girl you turned out
to be she would have believed in you
she'd want us both to be happy that's
why I have to make you disappear with
everything else that could haunt her
thoughts
you feel
always in desire
celestia forbid me from telling you the
truth your sister the one who exists
outside of fate was never meant to be a
horse girl with no soul she is at her
core a
witch reality has been undone and it
became your fantasy
the fantasy of the girl of illusions
why
because you are her opposite and if she
is the girl with nothing you are the one
with everything don't you see you've
always been the greatest of us all
you are you're my everything
[Music]
do you remember this day november 19th
of 2010
season 1 episode 6 of Friendship is
Magic it was the first day we met it
really was so much simpler i look back
at this time and remember who I was back
then you were just another obstacle to
me arrival and nothing more and yet here
we are look at how far we've come we
hold the fabric of reality in our hopes
i can reshape the world and still I'd
trade it all to live in this moment
forever when everything was simple
before I realized how much I needed you
i can fight fate sparkle I always have
but I don't know how to fight the one
fear you gave to me
the fear of what
the fear of knowing one day I might have
to live in a world without you
[Music]
nothing is going to take me away from
you i didn't pick you because you were
the greatest not because destiny handed
you something because it didn't you
don't have some kind of grand purpose or
divine rule like a
princess you had nothing and you still
fought harder than any pony that I know
you clawed your way to every triumph
even when the whole world would laugh i
never wanted to be this but only you can
be this only a girl who's been beaten
down as much as you can make fate take a
bow then why does it feel so empty why
does it feel like I've lost everything
because you traded it all away to hold
on to just one thing
you and I am grateful for it but it'll
be lonely if we're the only ones there
are so many ponies besides us and they
all deserve to live so please bring it
all back and
make all
Oh Trixie just when I thought you'd
disappoint you always bring it all
around is this what they call falling in
love
now I'm truly alone you found your long
lost sister got revenge against your
father erased reality and brought it
back then became a pegacorn because you
felt like it you don't get to mope like
a [__]
check it out dear the stolen hearts
they're going back to their natural
hosts
am I
here in
vain hold
on to the
night there will be no
shame i want to be with you and make
believe with you and live in harmony
harmony
[Music]
i want to be with you and make believe
with you and live in harmony harmony
hey will you marry
me we can give you what you want if
you'll let us i know it might not be the
perfect family you pictured for yourself
but we're all here for you and we love
you so very much
[Music]
will you be my wife Trixie Lulu
yeah of course I will
[Music]
all I want to be with you and make
believe with you and live in harmony
harmony i want to be with you and make
harmony
all i want to be with you and make
believe with you and live in harmony i
see
[Music]
all my
love i write to you in ink darker than
my
dreams you speak to me speak to
me in riddles all the hearts like there
is no
[Music]
need i can't believe I'm waking up to
feel your
naked in my bed
it's just like wild
[Music]
sand i'll be the host
tell me that I am the
strongest and all your new year
day throw away your
terms you choose your f you choose your
f your
fingertips play with the fabric of my
dress
lost in a
day so it's true huh the bastard really
did it i uncovered as much as I could
and indeed your family records were
heavily altered it looks like you did
have a twin sister named Marionette
apparently she came out sickly because
you sucked all the magic out of her
while in your mother's womb like a tiny
blue vampire so what you're saying is
I'm better don't use baby murder as a
flex it wasn't just your sister your
mother she held on for some time but she
became increasingly weak the only one
who came out healthy was you that
strength didn't come from nowhere are
you saying I killed her too probably why
your dad covered it up famous magicians
demon Spawn kills wife and baby it
doesn't exactly look great on a resume
then they're all gone my whole family
was killed by my hooves and my sister i
thought my life was hard but she she had
it so much worse and that bastard
jackpot covered it all up suddenly I
don't feel so bad murking that [__] my
only regret is that I didn't make it
last wow all right i was not ready for
that here I thought we were doing family
trauma not crime confessions dear please
don't go around confessing to being a
murderer just before our wedding it
would seem the great and powerful Trixie
is many things a murderer a talented
show pony an unintentional baby
vampire i wonder what Mary did all this
time what sort of life did she live i
guess I'll probably never get to know
hey let's not focus on that now you
promised to marry me remember
yeah I did then let's start and move
forward from there one step at a time
[Music]
ah were you waiting for us this whole
time obviously not i just happened to be
here so you weren't worried about Trixie
if anything I was worried about you poor
silly princess so soft and squishy if
Trixie broke down crying in there you
would have probably drowned in her tears
did you just talk with two voices at
once never do that again so uh how you
feeling Trix C i'm managing that's good
wouldn't want you falling apart after
everything I put together for you what's
that supposed to mean oh nothing just
that this all turned out pretty
perfectly you reunited with your long
lost sister uncovered a deep dark family
secret and got the ultimate gift of
becoming a peggacorn and best of all you
don't regret it one bit no more lies or
burdens just you your brand new set of
wings and the love of your life i'd say
this is a pretty happy ending all things
considered
oh so you do love us i literally never
said that you totally love us why else
do you keep following us around
everywhere we go yeah sweetie it's okay
to admit that you love us we understand
i'd sooner throw myself into a volcano
she loves us so much she's willing to
die for us i'm so touched okay i love
you
idiots happy i hate how much I love you
both i hate how much you get under my
skin and I especially hate how grateful
I am that you gave me life
oh look she's blushing
[Music]